(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-05T22:35:41.286948",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start in a short while.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Please be aware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
2nd Round Sales Goods
あ、こっちこっちこっち！
Ah, over here, over here!
今日、一人じゃないんですね。
You're not alone today, are you?
え？一人？
Eh? Alone?
さっきの、ここで会った人たち。
The people from earlier... we just met here.
ここ…
Here...
パレード
...parade
Joyしてこうぜ！
Let's Joy!
JOYSOUND X1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[On-Screen Text: The concert will begin shortly. Please wait.]
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
[On-Screen Text: Please be aware of flashing lights during the show. Cheering aloud is OK.]
LOCK ON 2次販売グッズ
[On-Screen Text: LOCK ON Round 2 Merchandise Sales]
天音かなた 1st Solo Live「LOCK ON」
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live: LOCK ON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start shortly. Please wait a moment.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
Attention to all visitors
2次販売グッズ
Second Round Merchandise Sales
Amane Kanata 1st Solo Live LOCK ON
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[On-Screen: Please wait a moment until the show begins]
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
[On-Screen: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.]
LOCK ON 2次販売グッズ
[On-Screen: LOCK ON 2nd Batch Goods Sale]
あ、あ、あ
Ah, ah, ah.
聞こえますか、皆さん？
Can you hear me, everyone?
イェーイ！
Yay!
本日は天音かなた 1stソロライブ「LOCK ON」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Amane Kanata's 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON" today!
天音かなたでーす！イェーイ！
I'm Amane Kanata! Yay!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
In order for you to enjoy the concert to the very end, I have a few announcements to make.
公演中の、撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Recording, photographing, or using recording equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
そして、
And...
みんな、万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、絶対に無理をせず、お近くのスタッフへお知らせください。絶対にね？
Everyone, if by any chance you start feeling unwell, please do not push yourself and let a nearby staff member know. Absolutely, okay?
絶対だよ？
Promise?
会場内での、モッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他の皆様の迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Mosh pits, stage diving, or throwing objects onto the stage are strictly prohibited, as they cause a nuisance to others and disrupt the performance.
ルールを守って盛り上がってください！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
イェーイ！偉い！
Yay! Good job!
本公演は、映像配信、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます！
For this performance, video broadcasting and photography cameras are in the venue, so the audience seats may be captured!
イェーイ！いいよな？
Yay! That's fine, right?
映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware in advance that video footage and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
はーい！ありがとう！
Okay! Thank you!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#打ち抜けかなた」なので、みんなハッシュタグを使って、配信で見てくれているみんなも、
Also, the live hashtag is #ShootThroughKanata, so everyone please use the hashtag, including those watching the stream...
お前らは、あの、帰り道かな？帰り道にね、あの、またハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
As for you guys here, maybe on the way home? On your way home, please use the hashtag to pump things up even more!
ありがとう！それでは、開演までもう少し、みんなで一緒に盛り上がっていきましょう！
Thank you! Now then, we have a little more time before the show starts, so let's get hyped up together!
どどん！前進！ ちゃんと歓迎して
Boom! Forward! Welcome me properly!
無敵の 覚悟の
Invincible, prepared...
うー、わっしょい！
Uhh... Wasshoi!
限界突破の
Limit-breaking...
星のアイドル
Star idol!
乗っけな！熱情！
Ride on! Passion!
咲き乱れうち最強！
In full bloom, we're the strongest!
望まれて 愛されて
Being wanted, being loved,
宇宙一な光を見せて
show me the brightest light in the universe!
失礼
So long...
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる
Tu tulu tu tu tulu
ぽいじゃん ぽいじゃん
It's "ish", yeah? It's "ish", yeah?
神っぽいな
God-ish
止めないで高鳴り
Don't stop this throbbing heart
鏡にはうつりたがり
That wants to be reflected in the mirror
Hey!
もう一度心揺らして
Shake my heart once again
Yeah Yeah Knock out
Knock out
Knock out Hey Hey!
そうテイクハイ（ハイ・ハイ・ハイ・ハイ）
So take high (high, high, high, high)
無敵のアイ（アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ）
Invincible eye (eye, eye, eye, eye)
行こうぜ
Let's go!
ホップ・ステップ・ステップ 行くよ近未来
Hop, step, step, towards the near future
ライ・ライ・ライ・ライ 切り開く
Future, future, future, future, carving our way
私召喚
Summon myself!
燃やせプライド
Burn my pride!
行くぞー！ ありやてぃがとう！
Let's go! Thank you so much!
深く息吐いて
Take a deep breath
待ち構えてた
That I've been waiting for
眩しさは
The radiance is...
狂い始めるカレイド
...a kaleidoscope starting to go mad
Knock out
Hey! Target!
聞き飽きたよ
I'm tired of hearing it,
遠吠えだろ
it's just howling, right?
夢見てても
Even if you dream,
起きてなきゃ意味がない
it's meaningless unless you're awake.
噛み付いても
Even if you snap at them,
勝たなきゃ
unless you win,
空回りで
it's just spinning your wheels.
音響かせ
Let the sound ring out!
踊らされて強がり
Dancing to their tune, pretending to be strong,
欲張りで華麗に
greedy and magnificent.
Say!
牙向け
Bare your fangs,
嘘でも負けない ただただただただ
I won't lose even if it's a lie, just, just, just, just...
勝つ！
Win!
等身大の君なんだ
You are just your true self
笑顔でいられる毎日を
These days where we can smile...
誇りたい 信じたい
...I want to be proud of them, I want to believe in them.
切り拓く未来
The future we carve open.
無敵のアイ（アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ）
Invincible eye (eye, eye, eye, eye)
行こうぜ
Let's go!
ホップ・ステップ・ステップ 行くよ近未来
Hop, step, step, towards the near future
ライ・ライ・ライ・ライ 切り開く
Future, future, future, future, carving our way
私召喚
Summon myself!
壊せプライド
Destroy my pride!
クラップしてください！
Please clap your hands!
独り 独り 独り 待った しゃがみ込んで
Alone, alone, alone, I waited, cowering down.
不安 不安 不安 ばっか また置いていかれちゃったんだ
Nothing but anxiety, anxiety, anxiety, I've been left behind again.
ちか ちか って 赤いシグナル 点滅中
Blinking red signal is flashing.
誰か ゆら ゆら 運んでって いなくなっちゃった
Someone, carry me away swaying, everyone has disappeared.
から から って から回った
Spinning and spinning,
確信犯だ 決定打
guilty with intent, the deciding blow.
がら がら にしちゃって
Making it completely empty,
また突っ立っちゃってんだ
and I'm just standing there again.
ふら ふら って まっさかさま
Dizzy and upside down,
嘘八百に塗れてんだ
smeared in a pack of lies.
あれ あれ 聞こえますか
Oh, oh, can you hear me?
それ 吐き出しちゃいなさいな
Just spit it all out.
決定だ 返答だ 嘲笑してんだ
Decisions, replies, they're mocking us,
僕が成したって見下して
looking down on what I have achieved,
ああ 抜け出した 壊滅的だ 自滅でした！
ah, escaped, it's catastrophic, it was self-destruction!
あわく あわく 浮かんでただけで
Just by faintly, faintly floating,
独りぼっちになって
I ended up all alone.
こうやって適度にいい子になるまで
Like this, until you become a moderately good child,
愛してあげるね 大丈夫
I will love you, it's okay.
どんどん 汚して 満たして
Keep dirtying and filling,
全部 どこかに置いて 燃やして
leave it all somewhere and burn it.
骨の髄まで ちゃんと奥まで
To the marrow of the bone, deep inside,
愛 愛 愛 ラブ
Love, love, love, love.
なりたい ありたい こっち足りない
Who I want to be, who I want to exist as, is not enough here,
足りないままに 満たしたくなっちゃって
wanting to fill it while still incomplete.
寂しいね 可愛いね
How lonely, how cute.
お胸に映ったお友達も みんな全部
Even the friend reflected on your chest, everyone, everything.
そう 指差して 言葉交わさず 撫で撫でしてあげるから
Yes, pointing fingers without exchanging words, because I'll pat your head.
こっちおいで 愛嬌が上手だね
Come here, you're good at acting cute, aren't you?
えっ えっ えっ やったね
Eh, eh, eh, you did it!
息が吸えたね
You could breathe,
息が吐けたね
you could exhale.
独りだけで今日も過ごせたね
You spent today all by yourself again, didn't you?
手が上手だね
You're good with your hands,
口が上手だね
you're good with your mouth,
泣いちゃったら すべて消えちゃうって
saying that if you cry, everything will disappear.
悪夢がそうだから 忘れて 全て塗れなくちゃ
Because nightmares are like that, forget them and get smeared in everything.
ありえないくらい 愛おしくて 愛おしくて たまらないけど
It's unbelievably lovely, so lovely I can't stand it, but...
多分一発じゃ 届かないから 届かないから もう一回
probably a single shot won't reach, won't reach, so one more time.
痛くたっていいから 痛くたっていいから
Even if it hurts, even if it hurts,
言えることがいいよね
it's good to be able to say it, right?
しゃあないね 気のせいじゃないもんね
It can't be helped, it's not just your imagination.
しゃあないね しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped.
ねんねしたいよね もういっちょ
You want to go to sleep, don't you? One more time.
しゃあないね しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped.
泣いても 泣いても 届かないね
Even if you cry and cry, it won't reach.
しゃあないね しゃあないね
It can't be helped, it can't be helped.
誰も返事しないもんね
Because nobody replies anyway.
あわく あわく 妄想だらけ
Just faintly, faintly, full of delusions,
傷つけたりしないで
please don't hurt me.
こんな嘘だらけの世界になっちゃって ごめんね
I'm sorry it's become a world so full of lies.
大丈夫
Don't worry,
安全圏にようこそ
welcome to the safety zone.
新しい世界に降臨
Descending into a brand-new world,
見捨てないから ずっと今日も一緒
I'll never abandon you, we'll be together today and forever.
あらあら 絡み付いて 勘違い 君にリアル
Oh my, wrapping around you, this misunderstanding becomes your reality.
誇り高き天使になるまで 愛してあげるね
I'll keep showering you with love until you become a proud angel.
大丈夫 どんどん欲で満たして
Don't worry, keep filling yourself up with desire,
震える背中に恋焦がして
yearn with passion for that trembling back.
うつむいちゃうくらい 笑っちゃうくらい ちゃんと愛、愛、愛、愛、ラビュー
So much you look down, so much you laugh, properly, love, love, love, love, I love you!
じ、自分、陰キャですから... ふふっ
Ah, I-I'm an introvert, you see... hehe.
あ、怖い！ 人間が怖い！
Ah, scary! Humans are scary!
あっち行って！ 見ないで！
Go away! Don't look at me!
でもちょっとは見て！
But... please look a little bit!
おどおど おどおど もどもど もどもど
Timidly, timidly, hesitantly, hesitantly,
悲しき陰キャのララバイラン
the sad introvert's lullaby run.
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
今日も、今日も 地に足つけろ！
Today, too, today, too, keep your feet on the ground!
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
世界で一番 乾杯して！
Give the biggest toast in the world!
袖が当たったら漏れる泣き声
A whimpering cry escapes if our sleeves even touch...
ひっ、あ、ふっ、えっ、あ、ひっ、うっ、うっ、あ
お呼びでないのは重々承知
I'm fully aware that I wasn't invited,
終わらない会議 始まる
yet the endless meeting begins.
うるせえ！
Shut up!
知らねえ！
I don't care!
見んな！
Don't look at me!
巡る気持ちと
My spinning feelings and...
葛藤
...conflict.
エンター
Enter!
エンターキーが押せない！
I can't press the Enter key!
今日も眩しんでごめんなさい
Sorry for finding it too bright again today,
ただ嫌われたくないだけなのだ
it's just that I don't want to be hated.
愛想笑い 限りあるわけだ
My fake smiles are bound to run out,
とば、とば、とば、とば！
so fly, fly, fly, fly away!
笑おう 笑おう 手の平で笑おう
Let's laugh, let's laugh, let's laugh in the palm of our hands.
（あはは、うふふ、なるほどですね）
Ahaha, ufufu, "Ah, I see..."
後悔 後悔 から回る空回り
Regrets, regrets, running in useless circles.
反省 反省 また反省だ
Reflecting, reflecting, reflecting once again.
胸の中では ワンツースリーよつのメロディ
Inside my chest, a one-two-three, four-part melody...
明日は今日より人間になりたい
Tomorrow, I want to be a bit more human than today.
大型スター！
Large-scale star!
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
僕らは部屋でハッピータイム
We have our happy time in our rooms!
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
飾るだけの僕で後悔中
Regretting that I'm only here for show.
空気を読むこと イクスタシー
Reading the room is ecstasy,
声の聞こえに耳を澄まし
straining my ears to catch every voice.
群れず 騒がず 関わらず
No crowding, no making noise, no getting involved.
そう、我ら 呼んだか「陰の者」
Yes, did you call us? "The dwellers of the shadow."
陰キャで作られるこの世界は
This world made of introverts
形の中の承認欲求を考えている
is constantly thinking about structured desire for approval.
誰が誰を巻き込んで
Who is dragging whom in,
なんのために生きてきた
and what have we been living for?
妄想と真実を同時に展開し
Unfolding delusion and reality at the same time,
そして最後にショートする
and in the end, we short-circuit.
そう、最後にするのである<
Yes, that is how it ends.
うわああああ！
Uwaaaa!
超苦手なシチュエーション
An ultra-uncomfortable situation!
やだやだやだやだ
No, no, no, no!
雑談トークの得意な奴<
People who are good at small talk...
やだやだやだやだ
No, no, no, no!
2人だけで乗ってるエレベーター
Being in an elevator with just one other person!
そう 我らはそう「陰の者」
Yes, that's who we are, "dwellers of the shadow".
陰キャに愛を！
Give love to introverts!
悲しき陰キャのララバイラン
The sad introvert's lullaby run.
目と目を合わせずごめんなさい
Sorry for not making eye contact,
ただ明るい人は眩しくて
it's just that cheerful people are too bright.
ただ息をするつつごめんなさい
Sorry for just breathing,
この会話もすべてがメンタルで
even this conversation is draining my mental energy.
今日も眩しんでごめんなさい
Sorry for finding it too bright again today,
ただ嫌われたくないだけなのだ
it's just that I don't want to be hated.
愛想笑い 限りあるわけだ
My fake smiles are bound to run out,
とば、とば、とば、とば！
so fly, fly, fly, fly away!
笑おう 笑おう 手の平で笑おう
Let's laugh, let's laugh, let's laugh in the palm of our hands.
（あはは、うふふ、なるほどですね）
Ahaha, ufufu, "Ah, I see..."
後快 後快 から回る空回り
Regrets, regrets, running in useless circles.
反省 反省 また反省だ
Reflecting, reflecting, reflecting once again.
鏡に映る自分も
Even my reflection in the mirror...
目を逸らした
...turns away its gaze.
明日は今日より人間になりたい
Tomorrow, I want to be a bit more human than today.
なりたい なりたい
I want to be, I want to be...
大型スター！
Large-scale star!
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
どうしてこんなに愛しいの
Why is this so precious?
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
僕らは部屋で飛んでいく
We fly away inside our rooms!
あーっと、おっと！ 陰キャのターン！
Whoa, look out! It's the introvert's turn!
一生歌うよ ありがとね！
I'll sing for the rest of my life, thank you so much!
あ... ふふ
Ah... hehe.
みんなー！
Everyone!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ちょっと水飲んで...
Let me drink some water...
水飲みますね、1回。
I'm going to take a sip of water, just a sec.
うわぁ、ちょっと待って！
Whoa, hold on a second!
おーい！
Hey!
みんな、ありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
はい、ということでですね、ヘイ、こんかなた！
All right, with that said... Hey, Kon-Kanata!
最高！はい、キャッチコピーは「握力50キロ、ギュッギュ、握りつぶしちゃうぞー」ホロライブ4期生、かなたそこと、天音かなたです！
Awesome! Yes, my catchphrase is "Grip strength of 50 kg, squeeze, squeeze, I'll crush you!" Hololive 4th generation, Kanataso, also known as Amane Kanata!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
ということでみんな、天音かなた1stソロライブ「LOCK ON」にお越しくださりありがとうございます！
So, thank you everyone for coming to Amane Kanata's 1st Solo Live "LOCK ON"!
いや、本当にね、あの、初めてのソロライブですよ！
Seriously, this is my very first solo live!
ちょっと皆さん、僕も念願でしたが、ちょっと会場のみま、みんなも、この日を楽しみにして待ってたんじゃないの？！
Everyone, this has been my dream, but wasn't everyone in the venue looking forward to this day too?!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いや、本当にね、僕の今までの活動、ちょっとここにね、気持ちとかも全部、みんなと一緒にぶつけていけたらいいなと思っているので、今日一日楽しんでください！
Seriously, I hope to pour all my feelings from my activities up until now into this with everyone, so please enjoy today to the fullest!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
はい、みたいな感じでね、あの、みんなアルバムいっぱい聴いてくれた？コールまじですごいじゃん！天界まで届くよ！
Yes, just like that, did everyone listen to the album a lot? The call-and-response is seriously amazing! It reaches all the way to the heavens!
すごい！覚えてきてくれたんだね、ギリギリだったのにありがとう！
Amazing! You memorized them for me, even though it was last-minute. Thank you!
ありがとうね！めっちゃギリギリやったのに、ありがとう。え、そして皆さん、ちょっとぜひ紹介したいものがありまして！
Thank you! It was really last-minute, but thank you. Oh, and everyone, there's something I definitely want to introduce to you!
なんと！今回ガールズバンドを率いてきました！
To my surprise, I brought a girls' band with me this time!
すごい！いや、もうね、僕の夢でしたね。ガールズバンドというものが。ありがとうございます。
Amazing! Wow, it was my dream to have a girls' band. Thank you so much.
ありがとうございます。本当に可愛い人達で。
Thank you. They are truly cute people.
イェーイ！可愛いんですよ、皆さん。あの、腕章も、生徒会の腕章のね、もう忘れ去られた初期の設定ですね。こちらも、つけてくれてるから。僕、あの、生徒会のね、あの、書記なんだけど、覚えてる？
Yay! They are cute, everyone. Um, the armbands too, the student council armbands—that forgotten early setting of mine. They're wearing them too. You know, I'm the student council secretary, but do you remember?
あ、覚えてるわ。書記だから、生徒会長じゃないからね、はい。
Oh, you remember. I'm the secretary, not the student council president, alright?
ありがとう。ありがとうね。という感じでですね、
Thank you. Thank you. And so...
あの、憧れ、夢だったソロライブとガールズバンド、そしてみんなが。ありがとう。配信でもね、配信の、配信の皆さんも見れてるかな？ありがとう。
Um, the solo live and girls' band that I yearned for and dreamed of, and all of you. Thank you. And on the stream, are the stream viewers watching too? Thank you.
これ、推しカメラっていうのがありまして。ちょっと配信上ではね、イェーイ！アピールしてるんで。
We have this "Oshi Camera" feature. So on the livestream, yay, I'm showing off!
まあね、現地にいるみんなも配信でも観てくれるだろうから、ちょっと可愛くアピっとくわね。
Well, since everyone here at the venue will probably watch the archive too, I'll show off my cuteness a bit.
可愛い？ありがとう！
Am I cute? Thank you!
すご。これ、脳汁がドバドバ出ますね。
Incredible. The adrenaline is really pumping.
ありがとうございます。ライブの感想も、コメントも「イェーイ！」「うおー！観てる！」って言ってる。観てる、観てる、観てるよ！ありがとう。ということで、
Thank you. For thoughts on the live, the comments are like "Yay!" "Whoa! I'm watching!" I see you, I see you, I'm watching you! Thank you. And so,
こうやってね、ライブの感想なんですが、ハッシュタグ「#撃ち抜けかなた」で。あの、配信で観てる皆さんも、
regarding thoughts on the live, please post with the hashtag "#UthinukeKanata". For those watching on the stream too,
現地の皆さんは帰り際とか、帰った後とかになるんですけど、「#撃ち抜けかなた」でたくさんポストしてください！
And for those at the venue, it'll be on your way home or after you get back, but please make lots of posts with "#UthinukeKanata"!
イェーイ！ありがとう。ありがとうございます。
Yay! Thank you. Thank you very much.
そしてなんとですね、ちょっと悲しいお知らせがここで...
And guess what, I have some sad news here...
YouTube、TikTokで無料チラ見せを観ている方は、ごめん、ここまでです！あー！
To those watching the free preview on YouTube and TikTok, I'm sorry, but this is the end! Ah!
「えー？！」「そんなー！」なんて言ってる、えー、ということでね、
You're all saying "Eh?!" and "No way!" Well, and so,
すみません、ここから有料になってしまいます。有料コンテンツですね。あんなすごいことが起きるかもしれませんよ！ええ？！やばい！
I'm sorry, but from here on, it becomes paid content. It's paid content. Some amazing things might happen, you know! Eh?! Oh my gosh!
ということで、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄から配信サイトへよろしくお願いします！何が起こるか分からない。
So, for those who want to keep getting hyped together, please access the streaming site from the description! You never know what might happen.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
そしてですね、ステージの変化、みんな気付いた？気付きましたか？
And also, did everyone notice the change on the stage? Did you notice?
すごいでしょ？さっきまで羽が開いてたんですけど、ご覧の通り閉じました。
Pretty cool, right? The wings were open until just now, but as you can see, they closed.
これ、まあ、やっぱりセオリーで考えますと、みんなの声が足りないってやつじゃないの？！
If we think about the standard rules for this, doesn't this mean everyone's voices aren't loud enough?!
もっと、もっと！もっと、もっと！もっと！
More, more! More, more! More!
来た！やるじゃん！
It opened! You did it!
やるじゃん、みんな！ありがとう。みんなのおかげで、羽も...
You guys did it! Thank you. Thanks to everyone, the wings also...
ね？
See?
開きましたよ！ありがとうございます！
They opened! Thank you so much!
みんなの...
Everyone's...
あ！
Ah!
もしシスターになれば、かなた可愛い？
If I were a sister, would Kanata be cute?
かなた！
Kanata!
可愛い、可愛い、可愛い
Cute, cute, cute...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ということでね、羽もまた... ありがとう！
And so, my wings... thank you!
開きました！
They opened!
みんなの声も出てきたので、
And now that everyone's voices are out,
次の曲、行ってみよう！
let's go to the next song!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!